HA HUU THANG

ANDROID DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am an Android Developer with ~4 years of experience designing, developing, testing, and maintaining Android applications in many projects. I always want to make the products with reusable, maintainable, readable, etc by using my experience. I always work hard and research new things to improve my skills.

INFORMATION

Mobile Phone: (+84) 972 380 035 Date of birth: May 25, 1996

E-mail: huuthang1125@gmail.com

Skype: huuthang1125

Current Address: Ho Chi Minh City

SKILLS

- Soft skills
- · Team-working
- Work independently
- Analytical and problem solving skills.
- Java/Kotlin
- Android Jetpack Components
- MVP/MVVM architecture
- Performance optimization
- Restful APIs
- UI/UX
- Sketch
- Agile

EDUCATION

FPT POLYTECHNIC DA NANG

Android application development 2014 - 2017 GPA: 8.3/10

EXPERIENCE

LINE Corporation

2019 - Present

Android Developer

BÉ YÊU

Be Yeu is a free application for mom-to-be and moms with babies under 5 years old.

Main features: Feeding post, chatting, charts, events, quiz game, product advertising, analysing data, etc...

- Responsibilities: Analysing functions, design UI, customizing views, managing source code
- Demo: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=vn.com.lana.beyeu

CinQsmile Vietnam 2018 - 2019

Android Developer

RECOG

Main features: Sales, feeding post, chatting, charts, etc...

- Demo: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=dev.android.vl.recog

Gcalls Vietnam

2017 - 2018

Android Developer

Gcalls Plus

The application is a call center software using VOIP technology

Personal applications

Mangat (Read comics Online) Real Estate Application